{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Asphalt Paving Repair Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40373/":{"taskOID":40373,"originalTaskOID":40373,"setID":667,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":1287,"questionDisplayText":"Area Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes the area where you want the work done?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2086,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Driveway","answerDisplayText":"Driveway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6733,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Walkway or sidewalk","answerDisplayText":"Walkway or sidewalk","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4604,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2711,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Game court (tennis, basketball, etc.)","answerDisplayText":"Game court (tennis, basketball, etc.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4578,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Parking lot","answerDisplayText":"Parking lot","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5364,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Road","answerDisplayText":"Road","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1288,"questionDisplayText":"Work Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Describe the work you need to have done. (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2432,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Fill cracks","answerDisplayText":"Fill cracks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2437,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Fill potholes","answerDisplayText":"Fill potholes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5227,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Repair settled area","answerDisplayText":"Repair settled area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5170,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Remove old asphalt","answerDisplayText":"Remove old asphalt","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5333,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Resurface with new layer over existing asphalt","answerDisplayText":"Resurface with new layer over existing asphalt","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5728,"questionDisplayText":"Slope of Area","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Describe the slope of the area needing work.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2505,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Flat","answerDisplayText":"Flat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5801,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Slight slope","answerDisplayText":"Slight slope","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6080,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Steep grade","answerDisplayText":"Steep grade","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5387,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Rolling","answerDisplayText":"Rolling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":13,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":1287,"questionDisplayText":"Area Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes the area where you want the work done?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2086,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Driveway","answerDisplayText":"Driveway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6733,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Walkway or sidewalk","answerDisplayText":"Walkway or sidewalk","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4604,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2711,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Game court (tennis, basketball, etc.)","answerDisplayText":"Game court (tennis, basketball, etc.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4578,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Parking lot","answerDisplayText":"Parking lot","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5364,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Road","answerDisplayText":"Road","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2086,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Driveway","answerDisplayText":"Driveway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6733,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Walkway or sidewalk","answerDisplayText":"Walkway or sidewalk","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4604,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2711,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Game court (tennis, basketball, etc.)","answerDisplayText":"Game court (tennis, basketball, etc.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4578,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Parking lot","answerDisplayText":"Parking lot","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5364,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Road","answerDisplayText":"Road","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1288,"questionDisplayText":"Work Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Describe the work you need to have done. (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2432,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Fill cracks","answerDisplayText":"Fill cracks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2437,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Fill potholes","answerDisplayText":"Fill potholes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5227,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Repair settled area","answerDisplayText":"Repair settled area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5170,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Remove old asphalt","answerDisplayText":"Remove old asphalt","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5333,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Resurface with new layer over existing asphalt","answerDisplayText":"Resurface with new layer over existing asphalt","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2432,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Fill cracks","answerDisplayText":"Fill cracks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2437,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Fill potholes","answerDisplayText":"Fill potholes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5227,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Repair settled area","answerDisplayText":"Repair settled area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5170,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Remove old asphalt","answerDisplayText":"Remove old asphalt","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5333,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Resurface with new layer over existing asphalt","answerDisplayText":"Resurface with new layer over existing asphalt","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5728,"questionDisplayText":"Slope of Area","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Describe the slope of the area needing work.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2505,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Flat","answerDisplayText":"Flat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5801,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Slight slope","answerDisplayText":"Slight slope","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6080,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Steep grade","answerDisplayText":"Steep grade","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5387,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Rolling","answerDisplayText":"Rolling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2505,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Flat","answerDisplayText":"Flat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5801,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Slight slope","answerDisplayText":"Slight slope","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6080,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Steep grade","answerDisplayText":"Steep grade","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5387,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Rolling","answerDisplayText":"Rolling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":13,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/40373/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40373,"taskName":"Asphalt Paving - Repair or Patch","taskDescription":"Repair or Patch Asphalt Paving","xmTaskDescriptor":"Asphalt Paving Repair Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":302,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"asphalt asphalt driveway patio patch","textMessagingName":"Repr Asphalt Paving","rolloverLongDesc":"Includes fixing potholes, cracks, crumbing edges, etc. To freshen the look \u0026 extend the life of the surface, many people apply a seal-coat every few years.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes fixing potholes, cracks, crumbing edges, etc","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Patch/Repair Asphalt Paving \u0026 Driveways. HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated asphalt repair contractors in your area.","htmlTitle":"Asphalt Repair Companies \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Repair Asphalt Driveway","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":56,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Asphalt Paving Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Asphalt Paving - Repair or Patch","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Asphalt Paving Repair Project","urlName":"Asphalt-Paving-Repair-Patch-or-Reseal","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Asphalt Repair Companies - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"asphalt,asphalt,driveway,patio,patch,paving","emcCategoryOid":-12055,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":667,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}